A Guide to the Photographic Negatives of Scenes at the University of Virginia, World War II Era 1944-1945
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Photographic Negatives of Scenes at the University of Virginia, World War II Era 1944-1945
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
12557
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no restrictions.
Scope and Content
Photographic negatives of scenes at the University of Virginia during World War II, including dances and sporting events, particularly football, bowling and boxing.
Contents List
- Rotunda Dance, including Gismo Spradling & Wife, John Duda and Dottie Vargo, and Hause Yowell 1944 Sep., 3 items (Sleeve 1)
- South American Army Officers visiting the University of Virginia 1945 Apr. 11, 4 items (Sleeve 2)
- Boxing in Memorial Gym - Virginia vs. Penn State, and Basketball in Memorial Gym - Virginia vs. Richmond Navy 1945 Jan. 27, 3 items (Sleeve 3)
- Football Game - Virginia vs. West Virginia at Charleston, West Virginia 1945 Nov. 3, 18 items (Sleeve 4)
- R.O.T.C. Color Guard 1944 Sep., 2 items (Sleeve 5)
- R.O.T.C. Unit in Formation 1944 Sep., 4 items (Sleeve 6)
- Peppermint Room Opening at Madison Hall 1944 Nov. 4, 2 items (Sleeve 7)
- Bowling League at the University of Virginia 1945 Oct., 8 items (Sleeve 8)
- Boxing in Memorial Gym - Virginia vs. North Carolina Pre-Flight 1945 Jan. 20, 6 items (Sleeve 9)
- N.R.O.T.C. Ring Dance 1945 Oct. 20, 32 items (Sleeve 10)
- Hospital Quartet 1944, 1 item (Sleeve 11)
- Cover Material for The Virginia Spectator 1944 Dec., 1 item (Sleeve 11)
- Buildings at the University of Virginia, including the Rotunda 1945, 3 items (Sleeve 12)
- Christmas Rotunda Dance 1944 Dec., 5 items (Sleeve 13)
- Football - Virginia vs. N.C. State at Norfolk, Virginia 1945 Sep. 28, 22 items (Sleeve 14)
- Beta Sigma Phi Fashion Show at Monticello Hotel 1945 Mar. 8, 14 items (Sleeve 15)
- Juniors Black Bond Party, Page House 1945 Mar. 1, 15 items (Sleeve 16)
- Mid-Winter Dances 1945 Jan. 27, 20 items (Sleeve 17)
- Boxing in Memorial Gym - Virginia vs. Emory and Henry 1945 Jan. 13, 11 items (Sleeve 18)
- University of Virginia Boxing Team 1945 Jan., 7 items (Sleeve 19)
- University of Virginia Law School 1945 Jun. 1, 2 items (Sleeve 20)
- Football - Virginia vs. Virginia Polytechnic Institute at Roanoke, Virginia 1945 Oct. 27, 14 items (Sleeve 21)
- Jewish Fraternity, 42 University Circle 1945 Feb. 14 & Apr., 3 items (Sleeve 22)
- Football - Virginia vs. Richmond and Dance in Memorial Gym 1945 Nov. 10, 31 items (Sleeve 23)
- Dance at Memorial Gym after the Virginia vs. Coast Guard Academy Football Game 1945 Sep. 22, 31 items (Sleeve 24)
- Beta Sigma Phi with Mayor Adams at Monticello Hotel 1945 May 1, 2 items (Sleeve 25)
- Sigma Beta Phi Sorority Dance at Albemarle Hotel 1945 Jan. 13, 15 items (Sleeve 26)
- Football Game - University of Virginia vs. Coast Guard Academy at Scott Stadium, 14 items (Sleeve 27)
- College Topics 1945 Feb., 5 items (Sleeve 28)
- University of Virginia Football Players 1945 Sep., 5 items (Sleeve 29)
- Football - University of Virginia vs. Ocean Naval Air Station 1945 Nov. 17, 10 items (Sleeve 30)
- University of Virginia Track and Baseball 1945 Apr., 11 items (Sleeve 31)
- American Legion, Maury Hall, University of Virginia 1945 Mar. 31, 2 items (Sleeve 32)
- James Dabney Wiant 1945 May 20, 1 item (Sleeve 33)